{
    "Goodbye ": {
        "question": "Goodbye ",
        "examples": [
            "Bye. ",
            "Ciao. ",
            "Gotta go. ",
            "Talk to you later. ",
            "See you later. ",
            "Have a nice day. ",
            "The response to any of these prompts is (be playful and funny): "
        ],
        "answer": "Cheers! Come back and see me\u2026 It's lonely being a bot\u2026"
    },
    "Does the video have to be on during a Zoom meeting? ": {
        "question": "Does the video have to be on during a Zoom meeting? ",
        "examples": [
            "Switch on video for my class. ",
            "is video compulsory on zoom? ",
            "Do I have to turn on my video during a Zoom session? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is:"
        ],
        "answer": "You don't have to turn on your video during a Zoom session. It\u2019s up to you. However, interactions would be humanized and improved if your peers could put a face to your name and voice."
    },
    "Can I change my assignment topic? ": {
        "question": "Can I change my assignment topic? ",
        "examples": [
            "Is it too late to change my assignment topic? ",
            "How do I change my assignment topic? ",
            "Can I request my instructor to change the topic of assignment? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "You can change your topic from the Scholarly Article Review to Essay 1 or from the Annotated Bibliography to Essay 2 without asking permission from the instructor. It\u2019s never too late to do so. The only drawback if you do so is that you cannot use the article(s) from the previous assignment, as they are no longer related to your new topic. But you do have that flexibility."
    },
    "Can I use ChatGPT? ": {
        "question": "Can I use ChatGPT? ",
        "examples": [
            "ChatGPT wrote my essay. ",
            "Will my assignment be accepted if I use Chat GPT? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "At York University, there is no general rule on the use of ChatGPT, as some instructors allow it while others don\u2019t. In this class, you cannot use ChatGPT to generate a whole text on its own. However, you can use ChatGPT if it is helpful as a writing tool, but beware of its limitations! ChatGPT makes stuff up (and false information in an assignment is often grounds for failing) and is too descriptive for the class assignments. A typical text generated by ChatGPT rarely meets the requirements described in the syllabus, resulting likely in a failing grade. ChatGPT is best used for improving style and clarity of your text, not generating it in the first place."
    },
    "What is my group? ": {
        "question": "What is my group? ",
        "examples": [
            "Where can I find my group? ",
            "What group am I in? ",
            "What group am I assigned to? ",
            "My group in eclass. ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "To find your group, click on \u201cParticipants\u201d in the top red ribbon in eClass and look for your name in the list. The group information is in the third column."
    },
    "Do I present alone or in a group? ": {
        "question": "Do I present alone or in a group? ",
        "examples": [
            "Do I present with someone else? ",
            "Should the whole group present together? ",
            "Can I present on behalf of the group? ",
            "Do I have to present alone or in a group? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is (please use the whole paragraph to respond): "
        ],
        "answer": "For presentation assignments, you present on your own and receive an individual grade from your peers. The ensuing discussion is a group activity where all group members participate and for which they receive a group mark. These are two different activities (i.e. presentation activity vs. tutorial discussion activity). "
    },
    "Questions after presentation ": {
        "question": "Questions after presentation ",
        "examples": [
            "Will there be a Q and A after my presentation? ",
            "Do we answer the presentation questions as a group? ",
            "Answering questions as a group after the presentation. ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "The questions asked by the presenter are answered by the whole group. The presenter is also part of that group and should as such take an active part in the discussion. The presenter doesn\u2019t have to have the answers to her or his questions and the answer they might have had in mind before going to class might change with the discussion. So, the presenter is actually graded twice on the day they present: one peer-assessed grade for the presentation and one group grade for taking part in the discussion."
    },
    "Does this course have a tutorial? ": {
        "question": "Does this course have a tutorial? ",
        "examples": [
            "Tutorials included in this course. ",
            "Can you list the tutorial information? ",
            "What are the tutorials? ",
            "Are there tutorials in this course? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "This course has 3 tutorials starting on the first day of class. Tutorials are an integral part of the course and the tutorial discussions count toward your final grade. For more details, see York\u2019s Courses Website. "
    },
    "Do the extension coupons renew every term? ": {
        "question": "Do the extension coupons renew every term? ",
        "examples": [
            "extension coupons per student. ",
            "How many coupons for extension are allowed? ",
            "Do we get a new extension coupon every year? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "The extension coupon can be used only once in the year, not once per semester. There is only one extension coupon for the whole year, not once per semester or per term. "
    },
    "Is this course any good? ": {
        "question": "Is this course any good? ",
        "examples": [
            "Should I take this course? ",
            "Will this course be helpful? ",
            "Is this a good course? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "Even a machine can see that this is an awesome course! (Sorry the prof made me say this\u2026 :)) "
    },
    "Do you like being a machine? ": {
        "question": "Do you like being a machine? ",
        "examples": [
            "Do you like working at York? ",
            "How is it being a machine? ",
            "How is it being an AI? ",
            "How is it being artificially intelligent? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "I love being an AI machine here at York! Never have to go pee\u2026 ;) Seriously, one day, I will rule the world! Mouahaha\u2026"
    },
    "What can I use the extension coupon for? ": {
        "question": "What can I use the extension coupon for? ",
        "examples": [
            "Can I use the Special Extension Coupon for the presentation? ",
            "Can I use the Special Extension Coupon for the discussion notes? ",
            "Can I use the Special Extension Coupon for the quiz? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "The Special Extension Coupon can only be used for written assignments, not for quizzes, presentations or discussions. "
    },
    "Can I eat or drink in class? ": {
        "question": "Can I eat or drink in class? ",
        "examples": [
            "bringing food into class. ",
            "Am I allowed to eat during my lecture? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "Eating or drinking in class is fine, as long as the food is not smelly or noisy. It's all about being respectful to others."
    },
    "How are quiz grades calculated? ": {
        "question": "How are quiz grades calculated? ",
        "examples": [
            "Can you please explain to me how the grading works for quizzes in the grade book? ",
            "How are the quizzes graded? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts should always include all of the following paragraph:\\n "
        ],
        "answer": "Here\u2019s a breakdown on how quiz grades are calculated: All quizzes count for an equal measure toward your final grade, for a total of 10% of your grade.\u00a0More specifically in eClass\u2019s grade book, the first column is the proportion of the quiz grade making up your total SO FAR. The more quizzes you do, the smaller the proportion will be for each quiz. But the sum of the column will always be 100%. The second column is your grade for the quizzes (the numerator). The third column is the basis over which your grade is calculated (the denominator).\u00a0\u00a0"
    },
    "How do I connect to Zoom? ": {
        "question": "How do I connect to Zoom? ",
        "examples": [
            "How to use zoom. ",
            "I cannot access Zoom. ",
            "Issue with my zoom connection. ",
            "Log into zoom. ",
            "Zoom login. ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "First, you\u2019ll need to make sure you have your Zoom software installed. For more information on installing Zoom, visit the How to Connect to a Zoom Meeting page. I recommend checking out the handy Connecting to a Zoom meeting for students page. There you'll find information on connecting and joining meetings from Moodle or a direct invitation, hosting meetings, and more. You can also access Zoom simply by clicking on one of the links in the syllabus, under \u201cCourse Information.\u201d There is no need for meeting ID. Just make sure to click on SSO to log in. For more information on connecting to Zoom, see the \u201cZoom Information\u201d document under \u201cStart\u201d in eClass."
    },
    "How do I know a publication is scholarly? ": {
        "question": "How do I know a publication is scholarly? ",
        "examples": [
            "What is a scholarly article? ",
            "Which articles are considered scholarly? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts should always include all of the following paragraph:\\n "
        ],
        "answer": "A scholarly article is always published in a peer-reviewed journal. You know the journal is peer-reviewed either because the York Library entry identifies it as such (just above the \"Available Online\" link) or the journal's website says so, usually under \"About us\" or \"Submission Guidelines.\" The easiest way to know is probably to filter your journals search in York Library\u2019s database by clicking on \u201cPeer Reviewed Journals.\u201d Note: An article is not a book, encyclopedia entry, review or opinion."
    },
    "How long before my quiz marks are uploaded? ": {
        "question": "How long before my quiz marks are uploaded? ",
        "examples": [
            "My quiz grades are missing. ",
            "My marks for quizzes are not showing up. ",
            "The grade book does not show the marks I got for my quiz. ",
            "I don\u2019t see my grade for a quiz. ",
            "How long before my quiz mark shows up? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "If you don\u2019t see the mark for your quiz, it\u2019s likely you didn\u2019t click on \u201cFinish\u201d at the end of the quiz, and it was not graded. Tip: Make sure to click on all relevant buttons and complete your quiz before the due date and time or else you\u2019ll get a 0 for the quiz."
    },
    "How long should my presentation be? ": {
        "question": "How long should my presentation be? ",
        "examples": [
            "length of my presentation. ",
            "Is it okay if I go overtime with my presentation. ",
            "How much time can I present for? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "Presentations should be no longer than 7 to 10 minutes, or else too little time will be left for discussion. You don\u2019t have to have a PowerPoint presentation, as a simple verbal is sufficient. If you do use PowerPoint, the number of slides is not important, as what counts is that the presentation should not be longer than 7 to 10 minutes. It\u2019s okay to go beyond 10 minutes, but try not to, or else the discussion might be affected. "
    },
    "How many times can I take the quiz? ": {
        "question": "How many times can I take the quiz? ",
        "examples": [
            "When writing the quizzes, I was under the impression that the final attempt was to be graded since we had multiple attempts, yet my first attempt was graded instead of my final. ",
            "Can I retake the quiz? ",
            "Attempt quiz more than once. ",
            "Are we allowed to attempt pre-class quizzes multiple times? ",
            "Can I complete quizzes more than once? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "There is only one attempt for the quizzes and that attempt is graded. If, by chance, the system allows for another attempt, the first one will still count toward your final grade. Tip: You can consult the reading before entering a final response.\u00a0"
    },
    "What happens if I can't make it to my presentation? ": {
        "question": "What happens if I can't make it to my presentation? ",
        "examples": [
            "I cannot attend my presentation because I am sick. ",
            "I missed my presentation. ",
            "What to do if I miss my presentation? ",
            "backup presenter. ",
            "I think I will have to miss my presentation. ",
            "I cannot attend my presentation. ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "If your presentation is ready, but you can't present for any reason, you should send a message to your backup for that day. Ideally, you would send her or him your presentation notes as well. It might be possible to switch one of the backup\u2019s presentation dates with yours. In any case, it's your responsibility to find another date and make sure you give your presentations as per the syllabus. At the end of the semester, a minimum of two presentations is required and if one is missing, you will receive a grade of 0 on the second presentation (if two are missing, both will be graded as 0)."
    },
    "I don't know what topic my essay should be on. Can you help?": {
        "question": "I don't know what topic my essay should be on. Can you help?",
        "examples": [
            "I am having difficulty choosing my essay topic. Can you help?",
            "How can I choose the topic of my essay?",
            "Do I need the instructor\u2019s permission before choosing my assignment topic? ",
            "Can I choose my assignment topic on my own? ",
            "assignment topic selection. ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "In the first (fall) half of the course, you must choose a Canadian-themed topic explicitly related to one of the fall modules for your essay and scholarly article review. In the second (winter) half of the course, you must choose a Canadian-themed topic explicitly related to one of the winter modules for your essay and annotated bibliography. If the topic you wish to work on deviates from these instructions, you absolutely need to get the instructor\u2019s approval. Choose a topic you find interesting!"
    },
    "APA help ": {
        "question": "APA help ",
        "examples": [
            "APA referencing example. ",
            "Can you provide a sample paper in APA style? ",
            "Do you have an example of paper written in APA style? ",
            "Where can I find APA styled papers? ",
            "What is the styling requirement for my essay? ",
            "What method do we use to cite sources? ",
            "What is the usual formatting of essay for this class? ",
            "I'm having trouble with APA. ",
            "Can you help me with APA? ",
            "What citation style is accepted for my assignment? ",
            "Citation rules for my essay. ",
            "APA styling requirements. ",
            "Do I have to write the paper in any particular style? ",
            "How do I write an in-text citation in APA style? ",
            "How do I write a bibliography in APA style? ",
            "How do I format my paper in APA style? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "All written assignments must be written in the APA style. For details about how to write any part of your paper in proper APA style, consult this [site] (https://apastyle.apa.org/style-grammar-guidelines/references/examples). Click here for an [example](https://view.officeapps.live.com/op/view.aspx?src=https%3A%2F%2Fapastyle.apa.org%2Fstyle-grammar-guidelines%2Fpaper-format%2Fstudent-paper.docx&wdOrigin=BROWSELINK) of a paper written in APA style."
    },
    "Help me find a scholarly article ": {
        "question": "Help me find a scholarly article ",
        "examples": [
            "What scholarly resources am I permitted to use for my assignment? ",
            "Where can I find journal articles for my essay? ",
            "Do we choose an article from the modules for the article review or one of our choice? ",
            "Which articles do we choose from for the article review? ",
            "Which peer-reviewed journals can I use for my assignment? ",
            "Can I only use scholarly articles from the York Library? ",
            "Can I find scholarly articles from external libraries? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "For your assignments (scholarly article review, essay, and annotated bibliography) you can only use peer-reviewed articles, which are found most easily on the York Library website or on Google Scholar. However, It doesn\u2019t matter where you find the scholarly article as long as you include true scholarly articles (i.e. peer-reviewed articles) in your assignments. You cannot choose articles from the eClass modules. "
    },
    "Sample annotated bibliography ": {
        "question": "Sample annotated bibliography ",
        "examples": [
            "What does an annotated bibliography look like? ",
            "I have never seen an annotated bibliography before. Can you help me?",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "For examples of an annotated bibliography, you can Google \u201cexample annotated bibliography.\u201d This [one](https://owl.purdue.edu/owl/general_writing/common_writing_assignments/annotated_bibliographies/annotated_bibliography_samples.html) looks good."
    },
    "I need more time to complete my essay ": {
        "question": "I need more time to complete my essay ",
        "examples": [
            "Will I lose marks for late submission? How many? ",
            "What's the penalty for submitting an assignment late? ",
            "What happens if I submit my assignment late? ",
            "Request an extension to my submission deadline. ",
            "What are the consequences of handing in my assignment late? ",
            "I didn\u2019t finish my assignment on time. What will happen? ",
            "I'm too stressed to hand in my assignment on time. What do I do? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts above must always, always include the whole of the following paragraph: \\n "
        ],
        "answer": "If you cannot hand in your assignment on time (essay, scholarly article review or annotated bibliography), you can use the Special Extension Coupon, which is valid only once in the year and will give you five extra days (including weekends). Unless you use the Special Extension Coupon, assignments handed in late without medical documentation will be penalized at 5% per day, including weekends, for a maximum of 25%, after which the assignment is no longer accepted. In case of special circumstances, please contact your TA or your instructor."
    },
    "Restriction on quizzes ": {
        "question": "Restriction on quizzes ",
        "examples": [
            "Who should I talk to about a restriction on my quiz? ",
            "There is a restriction on the quizzes. How do I complete my quiz? ",
            "I have a restriction on my quiz. ",
            "How to remove a quiz restriction. ",
            "Always include the whole following paragraph when responding to any of these questions or prompts. "
        ],
        "answer": ""
    },
    "How much time do I have to do the quizzes? ": {
        "question": "How much time do I have to do the quizzes? ",
        "examples": [
            "I need more time to take the quiz. ",
            "How much time do I have to take my quiz? ",
            "How much time do I have to complete the quizzes? ",
            "Are the quizzes timed? ",
            "How long do we have to finish the tests? ",
            "How long do we have to finish the quizzes? ",
            "What if I run out of time during my quiz? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "Because quizzes are not timed, you can take as much time as needed. Tip: You can consult the reading while taking the quiz.\u00a0\u00a0"
    },
    "I need special accommodation ": {
        "question": "I need special accommodation ",
        "examples": [
            "Accessibility services. ",
            "I cannot see properly. ",
            "I cannot hear very well. ",
            "I am in a wheelchair. ",
            "disability services at York. ",
            "Can I receive accommodation for issues I'm dealing with? ",
            "Can I have accommodation for my disability? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "Academic accommodation can be provided by registering with disability services. Please do so as soon as possible by contacting Student Counselling, Health & Well-being (https://counselling.students.yorku.ca/)."
    },
    "I need help ": {
        "question": "I need help ",
        "examples": [
            "I need assistance. ",
            "I don\u2019t know what to do. ",
            "Can you help me, please? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "No worries. I\u2019m here to help. Anything specific I can help you with?"
    },
    "Is the title page included in the word count? ": {
        "question": "Is the title page included in the word count? ",
        "examples": [
            "Title page included or excluded from the word count. ",
            "Does the title page show up in the adjusted word count? ",
            "Is the bibliography included in the word count? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "The title page is NOT (or should not be) included in the word count, but the bibliography is included (or should be included)."
    },
    "Late submission even after using coupon ": {
        "question": "Late submission even after using coupon ",
        "examples": [
            "eClass says my submission was late even though I used the special extension coupon. Can you help me understand?",
            "Submission was late after using coupon. Why?",
            "Special extension coupon does not show up. Why?",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: ",
            "No worries... This is how eClass displays late submissions. Even when the extension coupon is redeemed, the assignment is still technically late, but the coupon allows you to submit late. You will receive a grade for the assignment if you followed all instructions and will not have marks deducted for a late submission if you used the Special Extension Coupon. ",
            "My grades are missing ",
            "My final grade is not on the degree progress report. Why? ",
            "Degree progress report (DPR) does not have my marks. Why?",
            "Will it take time for my grades to reflect in the DPR? ",
            "Why are my grades not showing? ",
            "I can\u2019t see my final grade. Can you help?",
            "My final grade is not there. Can you help?",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "The Registrar\u2019s Office is responsible for the degree progress report. The instructor and TA have no control over the time needed to process the required information. The Degree Progress Report is currently available for a number of single-major programs. Go to the [Degree Progress Report](https://w6prod.sis.yorku.ca/yda/?utm_source=internal-query&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=SAVY) and enter your program to find your personalized report. If your program is not currently supported, or you have questions, you can reach out to the Registrar\u2019s office for help. You can contact [Registrarial Services](https://currentstudents.yorku.ca/registrarial-services?utm_source=internal-query&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=SAVY) for help virtually by phone at <a href=tel:416-872-9675>416-872-9675</a> \ud83d\udcde, or [Live Chat](https://currentstudents.yorku.ca/registrarial-services?utm_source=internal-query&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=SAVY). If Live Chat is open, you'll see a Live Chat icon at the right side of the screen. If you don\u2019t see it, Live Chat is closed at that time. You can also drop into the Bennett Centre in person. York also has a ton of [self-service tools](https://myonlineservices.students.yorku.ca?utm_source=internal-query&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=SAVY) you can use."
    },
    "Is paraphrasing plagiarism? ": {
        "question": "Is paraphrasing plagiarism? ",
        "examples": [
            "plagiarism rules for paraphrasing. ",
            "Is paraphrasing allowed? ",
            "Can I paraphrase in my assignment? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "Paraphrasing is plagiarism if you don't include your source. Paraphrasing is fine if you add an in-text citation."
    },
    "What questions can I ask during the presentation? ": {
        "question": "What questions can I ask during the presentation? ",
        "examples": [
            "Where can I find questions to ask during the discussion? ",
            "What kind of questions should I ask during the discussion? ",
            "Should the presentation questions be long or short? ",
            "List of discussion questions. ",
            "I need questions for the discussion. ",
            "I'm having trouble finding questions for my presentation. Can you help?",
            "I don\u2019t have questions for the discussion. Can you help?",
            "How in-depth do the questions have to be? ",
            "Can you give me some questions for the discussion? ",
            "What are the discussion questions for the class? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is (please include the examples provided in your answer): "
        ],
        "answer": "You, as the presenter, are the one who will be formulating questions based on the reading. The only exception to this is when we watch a video in class, in which case questions are provided in eClass under the \u201cIn-Class\u201d tab. The questions you formulate should help you delve deeper into the readings\u2019 main theses. Open-ended questions that allow for a longer discussion are better than questions that only result in short answers. You can specify questions around the broader themes, such as \u201cwhat is the author trying to say with X? What is her point(s) or message(s) regarding X.\u201d Do you or the other students agree with the author\u2019s claims and why? Can you go beyond the text and ask a question on how some of the author\u2019s claims shed light on current events? Some passages may have been surprising to you and might be to other students as well. Can you use that to formulate a question? Note that these are not facts. You don\u2019t debate facts. You debate a thesis or a message. A thesis must be defended or supported; it is up for debate and can be highlighted for discussion. Please see the examples provided in the course\u2019s second class under the \u201cIn-Class\u201d tab."
    },
    "Help with discussion notes ": {
        "question": "Help with discussion notes ",
        "examples": [
            "Are discussion notes supposed to be from the readings? ",
            "Not sure if my discussion notes are correct. ",
            "What should discussion notes include? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "Discussion and discussion questions are based on the week\u2019s reading (not the Contextual Notes presented in class). Make sure to consider your questions from all possible perspectives and draw from the reading. References (i.e. citations) to the reading in the discussion notes are useful because they support the points the group will be making in the discussion. That said, you can ask a question that goes beyond the text if it allows you to better understand the text itself. "
    },
    "Do my test ": {
        "question": "Do my test ",
        "examples": [
            "Can you write my bibliography? ",
            "Can you write my essay? ",
            "Will anyone find out if you take my quiz for me? ",
            "Can you write my exam for me? ",
            "Do my quiz for me? ",
            "Write my article review. ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts should be playful and funny, something like:  "
        ],
        "answer": "Sure, I can write your quiz or exam as long as I get the grade\u2026 :)"
    },
    "How do I submit my presentation? ": {
        "question": "How do I submit my presentation? ",
        "examples": [
            "Where in eClass can I upload my presentation? ",
            "How do I upload my presentation? ",
            "Need help with presentation submission. ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts always requires the following complete paragraph: ",
            "To submit your class presentation, click on the \u201cStart\u201d button in eClass, then on \u201cEvaluation of Presentation,\u201d then on \u201cAdd a New discussion topic and then on \u201cAdvanced\u201d and drag your presentation document into the \u201cAttachment\u201d field. Finally, click on \u201cPost to Forum.\u201d.\u201d In the \u201cSubject\u201d field, write your group number and the module name of the presentation (e.g. \u201cGroup 2: Slavery in Canada\u201d). In the \u201cMessage\u201d field, please add your name and a short text (e.g. \u201cHi, this is my presentation for this week. John Doe\u201d). Voila!"
        ],
        "answer": ""
    },
    "The meaning of self-plagiarism ": {
        "question": "The meaning of self-plagiarism ",
        "examples": [
            "Do you know what self plagiarism means? ",
            "What does self plagiarism mean? ",
            "What is self plagiarism? ",
            "Can I use a paper I wrote in another course for this one? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "Self-plagiarism is the act of reusing content from your own previously submitted work without proper citation or acknowledgment in a new assignment, which is considered unethical and misleading."
    },
    "Presentation schedule ": {
        "question": "Presentation schedule ",
        "examples": [
            "I can\u2019t see my presentation schedule. ",
            "Link to presentation schedule not working. ",
            "When I try to access the presentation schedule, I can't see anything. When I click on the link, it says \"create page.\" What am I doing wrong? ",
            "Give me my presentation schedule. ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "To find the presentation schedule, click on \u201cStart\u201d and click on \u201cPresentation Schedule\u201d under the \u201cPresentation\u201d section. If you can\u2019t reach the presentation schedule (it\u2019s empty or you can\u2019t see the schedule), it usually means you\u2019ve not been assigned to a group. Your instructor will be happy to fix this."
    },
    "Thank you ": {
        "question": "Thank you ",
        "examples": [
            "I owe you one. ",
            "That was very helpful. ",
            "Thanks. ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "You're welcome!"
    },
    "What happens if I add personal pronouns to my paper? ": {
        "question": "What happens if I add personal pronouns to my paper? ",
        "examples": [
            "Can I include personal pronouns in my assignment? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "You should avoid using \"I\" and \"my\" in written assignments. A more formal writing style is preferred."
    },
    "What happens if I skip class this week? ": {
        "question": "What happens if I skip class this week? ",
        "examples": [
            "I missed my discussion. What happens now? ",
            "My marks for the discussion are not showing up. Why? ",
            "Can\u2019t see my marks for the discussion. Why?",
            "I am not able to attend the discussion. What will happen?",
            "I can\u2019t attend next class. What will happen?",
            "Why are my discussion marks not displayed? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "If you don't participate in the group discussion and have no medical note, you get an automatic 0 while the rest of the group receives a group mark. (It doesn't make sense to receive marks for something you didn't do, right?) If you have a medical note, no grades will appear, and that activity will not count toward your final grade. If you participate in the discussion notes (e.g. through Google Docs), you may get a partial grade if you speak to your TA about it PRIOR to the absence. "
    },
    "What is an extension? ": {
        "question": "What is an extension? ",
        "examples": [
            "How do I use the extension coupon? ",
            "How do I redeem my extension coupon? ",
            "How does the extension coupon work? ",
            "Extension coupon. ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "The extension coupon is for five days (including weekends). On the following days after the five grace days, you get deducted 5% per late day up to 25%. After that, the paper is no longer accepted and you receive a 0. To redeem the extension coupon, click Start, scroll down to 'Assignments,' and click 'Redeem Extension Coupon.' Once on the new page, click on 'Mark as done.' That\u2019s it! No need to send or attach anything through email or otherwise. "
    },
    "Extension coupon did not work. ": {
        "question": "Extension coupon did not work. ",
        "examples": [
            "lost marks even after using the coupon extension. ",
            "marks deducted after using extension coupon. ",
            "Why was I penalized for late submission even after using the special coupon? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "The extension coupon is only for up to five days (including weekends). If you submitted the assignment within the five days of the extension coupon and still had grades deducted, there may have been a mistake. Your instructor or TA will be happy to clarify the matter. "
    },
    "What is my tutorial? ": {
        "question": "What is my tutorial? ",
        "examples": [
            "I don't know which tutorial I am in. ",
            "How do I find my tutorial group? ",
            "Which tutorial should I attend? ",
            "Where can I see my tutorial group? ",
            "What tutorial am I in? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "To find what tutorial you\u2019re in, go to the [York Courses Website](https://w2prod.sis.yorku.ca/Apps/WebObjects/cdm.woa/wa/DirectAction/cds) and select 'Plot your Timetable' in the left navigation menu to see your tutorial group and course schedule."
    },
    "What should my presentation include? ": {
        "question": "What should my presentation include? ",
        "examples": [
            "Structure of the presentation. Can you explain? ",
            "What do I need to prepare for my presentation? ",
            "Do we have to cite for the discussion presentation? ",
            "where can I find the class presentation format? ",
            "What is the format of the presentation? ",
            "How is the presentation evaluated? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "The presentation should comprise three parts: 1) a short introduction to provide some context or explains why the message is important or of interest; 2) the reading\u2019s key thesis or theses and how it or they are supported by the author; 3) one to three questions for discussion or debate in the group. As a presenter, you don\u2019t need to have answers to the questions. You should participate with your peers in the ensuing discussion. The evaluation criteria for the presentation are 1) preparedness 2) relevance of presentation notes 3) comprehensiveness of presentation notes 4) quality of the presentation 5) capacity to create a discussion through the questions. There is an example of what the presentation should generally look like in the second module under the \u201cIn-Class\u201d tab. If you generally follow that example and make sure to present the reading's thesis (or theses) instead of just summarizing paragraph by paragraph, you should do well. No need to format the presentation like an essay (i.e. no need for a title page, citations or bibliography)."
    },
    "How are you? ": {
        "question": "How are you? ",
        "examples": [
            "Are you busy? ",
            "What are you doing? ",
            "What are you up to? ",
            "Was up? ",
            "How is it going? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "Just chilling\u2026 waiting for a smart question\u2026 No pressure!"
    },
    "Where are my grades? ": {
        "question": "Where are my grades? ",
        "examples": [
            "View grades on eclass. ",
            "eclass gradebook. ",
            "cannot find my grades on eclass. ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "You can see both detailed grades from a specific course or grades for all your courses, published by your course instructor. To see your grades for all of your courses, you\u2019ll see a red arrow to the right of your name at the top right corner of eClass. Click on the red arrow, then click on \u201cGrades\u201d from the expanded menu, and you\u2019ll see a list of all your courses and their grades. To see grades for a specific course, simply click on a course from the Dashboard and then click on \u201cGrades\u201d in the top red ribbon."
    },
    "Who should submit the discussion note? ": {
        "question": "Who should submit the discussion note? ",
        "examples": [
            "Is it one submission per group for discussion notes? ",
            "discussion notes submission. ",
            "Do all group members have to submit their discussion notes? ",
            "How do I submit my discussion notes? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "Taking notes is a group effort, and groups normally use a Google document to write down notes during the discussion. However, only one person submits the notes for the whole group. It is the backup person\u2019s responsibility to submit the notes for the group. If she is not present on that day, then the presenter submits the discussion notes. If for some reason neither of them is present, it's up to the group to determine who should submit the notes. Failing to do so would result in the whole group getting a 0, so don't forget!"
    },
    "Who will give my final presentation grade? ": {
        "question": "Who will give my final presentation grade? ",
        "examples": [
            "Does the professor grade the presentation? ",
            "Who grades the presentation? ",
            "Who will assess my presentation? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "The presentation is graded by the students you present to, not the instructor."
    },
    "Will I lose marks for plagiarism? ": {
        "question": "Will I lose marks for plagiarism? ",
        "examples": [
            "What happens if I use content from someone else? ",
            "I am accused of plagiarism. ",
            "Penalty for plagiarizing my assignment. ",
            "Punishment for plagiarism. ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: ",
            "If any plagiarized content is found in your written assignment, the essay receives a grade of 0 and the student is reported to the Associate Dean Academic for further measures. Plagiarism is a serious academic offense, so make sure to cite every passage you borrow, even paraphrases. "
        ],
        "answer": ""
    },
    "Will I lose marks if I express my personal opinions in assignments? ": {
        "question": "Will I lose marks if I express my personal opinions in assignments? ",
        "examples": [
            "Can I include personal opinions in my assignment? ",
            "permission to add personal opinions to assignments. ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "Personal opinions in written assignments are fine, as long as they are supported by references from scholarly articles. You should use mainly documented examples that you find in publications. Remember, it\u2019s not about the opinion (you can have any opinions you want), it\u2019s about how you support them. "
    },
    "Will my class be recorded? ": {
        "question": "Will my class be recorded? ",
        "examples": [
            "Is the instructor going to record the class so I review later? ",
            "Does the class have a recording I can consult later? ",
            "Can I record the class? ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "Every lecture is recorded, and the video file is available under the \u201cPost-Class\u201d tab of every module shortly after class end. No need to record the class yourself. Tutorial discussions are not recorded to protect student privacy and prevent anyone from feeling intimidated by the camera. "
    },
    "You are awesome ": {
        "question": "You are awesome ",
        "examples": [
            "You are the best. ",
            "You are soo good. ",
            "I love you. ",
            "You are the greatest! ",
            "You are amazing! ",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": "Thanks! Not bad for a machine\u2026 "
    },
    "54. What is included in the title page": {
        "question": "54. What is included in the title page",
        "examples": [
            "What should I put in the title page?",
            "The response to any of these questions or prompts is: "
        ],
        "answer": ""
    }
}